<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bloc</string>

    <string name="hello_bullhorn_fragment">Hello Bullhorn fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_campaigns_fragment">Hello Campaigns fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_accounts_fragment">Hello accounts fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_bloc_fragment">Hello bloc fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_messages_fragment">Hello messages fragment</string>

    <string name="bloc_frag_strongmoves">#StrongMoves</string>
    <string name="bloc_check_us_out">Check Us Out</string>
    <string name="bloc_members1516_desc">2014-2015 BLOC Members. Bridges Hall of Music. Pomona College</string>
    <string name="header_5corg_text">A Claremont Colleges Organization</string>
    <string name="header_whoarewe_text">Who Are We</string>
    <string name="worldcampus_text">The World Is Our Campus</string>
    <string name="header_brohood_text">Brotherhood. Community. Unity.</string>
    <string name="whoarewe_text">At its foundation, BLOC represents the formation of a community! In particular, the BLOC community is designed to be a locus for the support and promotion of the Black men at Pomona College. This community is active at Pomona College and is maintained by its members. These members include any and all men on campus actively in support of the unity, strength and voice of the marginalized men at the 5 C’s. The core values of the group have four direct points of impact: Social Unity, On-Campus Activism, Off-Campus Community Organization, and Academic Promotion. The first aspect of Social Unity represents the formation of the community through the induction of new members, the interactions at meetings, communication with alumni and presentation of BLOC produced events. On-Campus Activism reflects the ideology of the members of the organization in standing behind one another and behind the community of color at Pomona. Off-Campus Community Organization has been on going through collaborations with local high schools in the area and the specific community programs initiated by BLOC members. The last most important aspect of the core values, Academic Promotion, represents an emerging focus on the educational support and professional development of BLOC’s own members.These four points of emphasis focus the BLOC community towards a specific and achievable goal.</string>
    <string name="mission_text">BLOC is a crucial resource for self-identified marginalized—but in no way marginal—students. BLOC is a supportive extended family at the sometimes-alienating Claremont Colleges. BLOC is a tight-knit brotherhood; let this be most sacred. BLOC promotes academic achievement and celebrates members’ successes. The organization recognizes, takes on, and tries to mitigate hardship as exercises in collective compassion.\n\nBLOC members hone skills that will benefit them throughout their lives. Leadership opportunities prepare members for success in their chosen careers and, more importantly, as human beings. BLOC creates well-rounded programs and strives for excellence and quality in all its undertakings. Members, both individually and collectively, work toward the advancement of the campus community and broader communities. In doing so, BLOC contributes to the betterment of each member.\n\nBLOC harnesses its tight-knit brotherhood to collaborate with other people, groups, and communities. BLOC hopes to assess the local climate in order to gauge the needs of the underrepresented. BLOC fosters close partnerships within the 5C community to achieve common goals. By embarking on these endeavors together, BLOC seeks mediation, reconciliation, and understanding. Co-curricular activities can be as valuable as the classroom experience; hence, BLOC promotes involvement in all aspects of collegiate life.</string>

    <!-- image descriptors -->
    <string name="chevron">chevron_down</string>
    <string name="menu_bullet">menu bullet</string>

    <string name="header_mission">Mission</string>
    <string name="header_constitution_text">The Bloc Constitution</string>
    <string name="article1_header">Article I - Name</string>
    <string name="article2_header">Article II - Mission</string>
    <string name="article3_header">Article III - Membership</string>
    <string name="article4_header">Article IV - The Executive Board of BLOC</string>
    <string name="article5_header">Article V - Elections</string>
    <string name="article6_header">Article VI - Meetings</string>
    <string name="article7_header">Article VII - BLOC Advisor</string>
    <string name="article8_header">Article VIII - Website</string>
    <string name="article9_header">Article IX - Anti-Discrimination Clause</string>
    <string name="article10_header">Article X - Amendments</string>
    <string name="article11_header">Article XI - Ratification</string>
    <string name="article1_text">The title of the organization is Building Leaders on Campus (BLOC).</string>
    <string name="article2_text">BLOC is a crucial resource for self-identified marginalized—but in no way marginal—students.  BLOC is a supportive extended family at the sometimes-alienating Claremont Colleges.  BLOC is a tight-knit brotherhood; let this be most sacred.  BLOC promotes academic achievement and celebrates members’ successes.  The organization recognizes, takes on, and tries to mitigate hardship as exercises in collective compassion.\n\nBLOC members hone skills that will benefit them throughout their lives.  Leadership opportunities prepare members for success in their chosen careers and, more importantly, as human beings.  BLOC creates well-rounded programs and strives for excellence and quality in all its undertakings.  Members, both individually and collectively, work toward the advancement of the campus community and broader communities.  In doing so, BLOC contributes to the betterment of each member.\n\nBLOC harnesses its tight-knit brotherhood to collaborate with other people, groups, and communities.  BLOC hopes to assess the local climate in order to gauge the needs of the underrepresented.  BLOC fosters close partnerships within the 5C community to achieve common goals.  By embarking on these endeavors together, BLOC seeks mediation, reconciliation, and understanding.  Co-curricular activities can be as valuable as the classroom experience; hence, BLOC promotes involvement in all aspects of collegiate life.</string>
    <string name="article3_text">Section III.01 - Admission\n\t\t1. BLOC actively seeks underrepresented students at the Claremont Colleges.\n\t\t2. BLOC determines membership at the end of the four-week initiation process at the beginning of each fall semester of classes at the Claremont Colleges.\n\nSection III.02 - Initiation - Incomplete\n\t\t1. Proposed\n\t\t\t\ta. Check out BLOC/Preview Period to allow drop-outs (maybe first 2 meetings after the very first meeting)\n\t\t\t\tb. Fall only or Fall &amp; Spring admission?\n\nSection III.03 - Requirements for Active Members\n\t\t1. Active members of BLOC are required to attend all meetings unless due to unforeseeable reasons (e.g. – academics, health, etc.).  Attendance will be taken at every meeting.\n\t\t2. BLOC membership must be brought into question and analyzed if more than fifty percent of meetings are unexcused absences for the given school year.\n\t\t3. Executive Board members review absences at the Executive Board meetings, determine individuals (including Executive Board members themselves) membership, and update the official membership list in the online member center.  The executive board will discuss these absences and provide support as needed for those in question.\n\t\t4. Executive Board members deliberate consequences over any BLOC member guilty of a Claremont College student violation or other serious offense.\n\t\t5. Active participation is necessary for membership.  This is defined as consistent involvement with event planning, hosting, tabling, mentoring, etc.\n\t\t6. Each member must pay dues each semester.\n\nSection III.04 - Entitlements\n\t\t1. Membership entitles each member to have a say in what BLOC does as an organization.\n\t\t2. Every active member must be aware of decisions made on behalf of BLOC; every active member is entitled to a vote before BLOC sponsors, puts its name on something, or publishes something as it reflects the views, opinions, and commitment of each member to be in some way involved with that decision as a member of BLOC.</string>
    <string name="article4_text">Section IV.01 - Officers\n\t\t1. President\n\t\t2. Vice President\n\t\t3. Treasurer\n\t\t4. Two Community Ambassadors\n\t\t5. Historian\n\t\t6. Academic Chair\n\t\t7. Social Chair\n\t\t8. Communications Chair\n\nSection IV.02 - Qualifications for Office\n\t\t1. General Eligibility for any Office\n\t\t\t\t A. A member seeking office must have one hundred percent participation at BLOC meetings excluding excused absences.\n\t\t\t\t B. A member seeking office must have completed one semester at one of the Claremont Colleges, graduate or undergraduate.  \n\t\t2. Requirements for the Position of President\n\t\t\t\t A. The candidate must have been a member of BLOC for at least two years.\n\t\t\t\t B. The candidate must have completed at least two years at one of the Claremont Colleges, graduate or undergraduate.\n\t\t3. Requirements for the Position of Vice President\n\t\t\t\t A. The candidate must have been a member of BLOC for at least one year.\n\nSection IV.03 - Vacancy of Office \n\t\t1. In the rare case the President leaves for a semester:\n\t\t\t\t A. The current Vice President becomes assumes the presidency.\n\t\t\t\t B. A new Vice President is elected by the special election process.\n\t\t\t\t C. Any member who meets the eligibility requirements for an office is eligible to run for that office.\n\nSection IV.04 - The Duties of the Presidency\n\t\t1. Oversees all BLOC activities:\n\t\t\t\t A. Is responsible for Executive Board decisions\n\t\t\t\t B. Oversees BLOC’s progression toward goals\n\t\t\t\t\t\t 1) Ensures the communication of status reports\n\t\t\t\t C. Accounts for general membership’s minimum requirements\n\t\t\t\t D. Facilitates the meetings\n\t\t\t\t\t\t 1) Opens Meetings\n\t\t\t\t\t\t 2) Introduces Announcements\n\t\t\t\t\t\t 3) Closes Meetings\n\t\t\t\t E. Is accessible on a daily basis\n\t\t\t\t\t\t 1) By phone, email, and direct contact\n\t\t\t\t\t\t 2) Maintains accountability\n\t\t\t\t F. Actively reprimands BLOC members who fail to uphold all duties, rules, and requirements placed upon group member\n\t\t\t\t G. Keeps his official activities transparent\n\t\t\t\t H. Stays abreast of all the topics relating to BLOC\n\nSection IV.05 - The Duties of the Vice President\n\t\t1. He assumes all duties of the Presidency in the President’s absence.\n\t\t2. He oversees logistics.\n\nSection IV.06 - The Duties of the Community Ambassador\n\t\t1. He coordinates community service opportunities.\n\t\t2. He is the liaison to the Draper Center.\n\t\t3. He forms relations with off campus organizations.\n\t\t4. He keeps record of member attendance at community service events.\n\t\t5. He organizes logistics of community service.\n\nSection IV.07 - The Duties of the Treasurer\n\t\t1. He works closely with the other officers to organize financial plans for events.\n\t\t2. He keeps records of financial transactions.\n\t\t3. He manages the PayPal and Bank of America financial accounts.\n\t\t4. He provides a financial outlook on a monthly basis.\n\t\t5. He searches for financial opportunities, such as grants and fundraisers.\n\t\t6. He provides help to the other officers beyond finances when necessary.\n\nSection IV.08 - The Duties of the Historian\n\t\t1. He keeps notes from meetings.\n\t\t2. He collaborates with the Presidents to create the agenda for meetings.\n\t\t3. He uploads agenda to Google Drive and shares it with all active members at least twenty hours before meetings.\n\t\t4. He assists the Vice President with handling public relations.\n\t\t5. He has access to a computer during the meetings.\n\t\t6. He keeps track of attendance of members at meetings and logs it on the Google Drive Attendance folder for the appropriate period.\n\t\t7. He keeps track of seminars attended.\n\t\t8. He ensures every member, past and present, has organized and updated his own contact information in the Google Drive Member Center/Database.\n\t\t9. He makes sure that the BLOC Google Drive is kept updated, in order, and that all documents remain or are put in its appropriate folder.\n\nSection IV.09 - The Duties of the Academic Chair\n\t\t1. He meets with each class to assess overall goals, and will meet with individual members to set academic goals for the semester as necessary.  He must meet individually with every new member.\n\t\t2. He ensures that every member has access to campus resources.\n\t\t3. He pairs members in need of academic support with a mentor from within the BLOC organization.\n\nSection IV.10 - The Duties of the Social Chair\n\t\t1. He is aware of events on and off campus.\n\t\t2. He manages social events.\n\t\t\t\t A. He will serve as point person for social events.\n\t\t\t\t B. He will manage the social hosts.\n\t\t\t\t C. Creates and maintains the Facebook event pages. \n\t\t3. He is responsible for the booking of spaces and necessary equipment and other materials necessary for an event.\n\nSection IV.11 - The Duties of the Communications Chair\n\t\t1. He is responsible for actively managing the group email account.\n\t\t2. He oversees the newsletter and each social media site:\n\t\t\t\t A. Facebook\n\t\t\t\t B. Google+\n\t\t\t\t C. GroupMe\n\t\t\t\t D. Instagram\n\t\t\t\t E. LinkedIn\n\t\t\t\t F. Twitter\n\t\t3. He posts relevant, appropriate, and insightful content to each of the above social media service BLOC pages at least once every two weeks.\n\nSection IV.12 - Length of Term\n\t\t1. All officers assume their offices immediately after being elected.\n\t\t2. All offices are held for no longer than one school year, two consecutive semesters.</string>
    <string name="article5_text">Section V.01 - The Electoral Process\n\t\t1. All officers are elected at the end of the spring semester.\n\t\t2. Nominees are self-nominated and elected by the general body.\n\t\t3. Voting is executed by each member eligible by casting his vote on a paper and handing it to the President.\n\t\t4. The President shall tally the votes. \n\t\t5. During the voting process for an office, the candidates running for the respective office must not be present in the meeting room while voting occurs, as they are not eligible to vote.\n\t\t6. A simple majority of the votes secure the office.\n\nSection V.02 - Special Elections\n\t\t1. A vacancy of an office requires a special election to choose new officer.\n\t\t2. If the office of the President is vacant, the current Vice President shall assume the office.\n\nSection V.03 - Impeachment\n\t\t1. The complaining party and accused officer must present their cases to the main body for review.\n\t\t2. In the event of Presidential impeachment, the Vice President shall organize the impeachment process.\n\t\t3. For offices besides the President, the President shall organize the impeachment process.\n\t\t4. Two thirds of the main body must vote for the officer in question to be removed.\n\t\t5. If impeached, the officer shall be removed immediately, and a special election shall be held for the office.\n\t\t6. In the case of the impeachment of the President, the current Vice President take on the office and a special election shall take place for the office of Vice President.</string>
    <string name="article6_text">Section VI.01 - Executive Meeting\n\t\t1. The Officers shall have a weekly meeting during the Claremont Colleges school year.\n\t\t2. The officers shall determine the best time and location for the meeting.\n\nSection VI.02 - Advisor Meeting:\n\t\t1. A monthly meeting shall take place between the Executive Board and the staff or faculty advisor.\n\t\t2. The location and time shall be determined by the advisor and officers.\n\nSection VI.03 - General Body Meetings\n\t\t1. A weekly meeting of BLOC members shall take place at a location chosen by the officers.\n\nSection VI.04 - Emergency Meetings\n\t\t1. Only the President has the authority to call an emergency meeting.\n\nSection VI.05 - Quorum\n\t\t1. A vote shall take place when seventy percent of active BLOC members are present.\n\t\t2. A quorum must be reached to vote on all issues.\n\t\t 3. If a quorum is not reached, the issue shall be set aside.\n\t\t4. If in two weeks in a row, a quorum does not exist, then the issue can be voted upon at the next meeting.</string>
    <string name="article7_text">Section VII.01 - Eligibility\n\t\t1. The advisor shall be a staff or faculty member of the Claremont Colleges who is receptive to and can identify with members of BLOC.\n\t\t2. The advisor is voted on by the body by a simple majority vote.\n\nSection VII.02 - Duties\n\t\t1. He attends monthly meetings with officers based on his schedule.\n\t\t2. He serves as a representative to faculty and staff of the Claremont Colleges.</string>
    <string name="article8_text">Section VIII.01 - Domain\n\t\t1. The domain of the official BLOC website is blocorganization.org.\n\t\t2. Marcellus Demer is the legal owner of this domain until BLOC deems a successor.\n\t\t3. The domain shall be registered to him until death, until he is no longer physically capable to manage the domain, he desires to pass it down to another member of BLOC, until an amendment to this Constitution is passed that forces him to retire ownership of the domain, or until BLOC deems a suitable successor.\n\nSection VIII.02 - Webpage\n\t\t1. The webpage is designed by Irving Torres &amp; Marcellus Demer.\n\t\t2. Marcellus or his successors, as webmaster, is required to work with all members of BLOC to keep all content and information relevant and updated, up to the discretion of the residing President.</string>
    <string name="article9_text">BLOC does not discriminate on the basis on race, color, creed, national origin, sexual orientation, religion, age, disability or other legally protected status in admission to, access to, or operations of its programs, services, or activities. </string>
    <string name="article10_text">Section X.01 - Eligibility\n\t\t1. Any member, past or current, of BLOC is able to propose amendments to the BLOC Constitution.\n\nSection X.02 - Process\n\t\t1. A member wishing to make amendments to the BLOC Constitution must:\n\t\t\t\t A. Download the BLOC Constitution from the Google Drive and open it in Microsoft Word or open it on the Google Drive.\n\t\t\t\t B. Ensure that the track changes feature is enabled.\n\t\t\t\t C. Make any edits he wishes to make.\n\t\t\t\t D. Save and upload the document with a different file name (e.g. Draft) to the Constitution folder in the Google Drive.\n\t\t\t\t E. Inform the President that this process has been done.\n\nSection X.03 - Voting on Amendments\n\t\t1. The President shall schedule a vote within the next two general body meetings after he receives notice of amendments.\n\t\t2. The draft must be projected on screen for the members in attendance to see or printed out before hand for everyone to see.\n\t\t3. The track changes feature shall be used to approve or deny each change logged in either Microsoft Word or Google Docs.\n\t\t4. An amendment may not be approved if it has grammatical errors or does not logically make sense.\n\t\t5. A change may only be approved if during the vote, seventy percent of members vote in favor of approving the change; otherwise, the change must be denied.\n\t\t6. Voting is done by standard voting procedures.\n\t\t7. Voting may take place over several meetings if they cannot be finished within the setting of one meeting.\n\nSection X.04 - New Constitution\n\t\t1. If one or more amendments are passed after a single proposal, it becomes part of the new BLOC Constitution.\n\t\t2. The new BLOC Constitution must be uploaded or saved on the Google Drive in the appropriate folder alongside of all old versions of the Constitution.\n\t\t3. New amendments shall take effect seven days after they are ratified.\n\t\t4. The new BLOC Constitution must be printed out and given to each active BLOC member to ensure everyone has their own individual, physical, updated copy.</string>
    <string name="article11_text">Section XI.01 - Voting\n\t\t1. Seventy percent of active members must vote in favor of the Constitution for it to be ratified.\n\t\t2. The document must be spellchecked with no errors before being ratified.\n\nSection XI.02 - Effect\n\t\t1. This BLOC Constitution is a living document that must not only be available online to all BLOC members in the Google Drive, but also must be printed and handed out to each new BLOC member so that each member has his own individual copy.</string>

    <string name="placeholder">placeholder</string>
    <string name="lightning">Natural Lightning</string>
    <string name="color_baloons">Color Baloons</string>
    <string name="natural_wall">Natural Wall</string>

    <string name="bloc_president">President</string>
    <string name="bloc_copresident">Co-President</string>
    <string name="bloc_historian">Historian</string>
    <string name="bloc_communityambassador">Community\nAmbassador</string>
    <string name="bloc_socialchair">Social Chair</string>
    <string name="bloc_treasurer">Treasurer</string>
    <string name="bloc_academicchair">Academic\nChair</string>
    <string name="bloc_communicationschair">Communic-\nations Chair</string>
    <string name="bloc_general_text">Leaders Building on Campus</string>

    <string name="bloc_president_name">Olufela Koleoso</string>
    <string name="bloc_copresident2_name">Zach Williams</string>
    <string name="bloc_copresident1_name">Dylan Goodman</string>
    <string name="bloc_socialchair_name">Triston Caviness</string>
    <string name="bloc_communityambassador_name">Ellington\n&amp; Ivan</string>
    <string name="bloc_academicchair_name">Christian,\nBen &amp; Aaron</string>
    <string name="bloc_communicationschair_name">Tristan</string>
    <string name="bloc_treasurer_name">Reuben Murray</string>
    <string name="bloc_historian_name">Ivan Solomon</string>

</resources>
